ACTWU's Research Department Company Records 5619/012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACTWU's Research Department Company Records
1937-1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Research Department
Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union. Research Department
5619/012
101 cubic feet
101 linear ft.
Correspondence, reports, publications.
This collection consists of correspondence, newspaper clippings, financial reports, Securities and Exchange Commission reports, Dunn and Bradstreet reports compiled by the Research Departments of ACWA and ACTWU, regarding companies the union had organized or was looking to organize. The materials are filed in alphabetical order by company name.
6766482
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff
Date completed:
July 2010
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 2011
Biographical / Historical
The Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, the most significant union representing workers in the men's clothing industry, was founded in New York City in 1914 as a breakaway movement from the United Garment Workers. Radical and immigrant workers in the tailors' and cutters' locals were the core of the seceding group, which advocated industrial unionism and economic strikes in opposition to the UGW's craft organization, which they saw as conservative and timid. Their diverging views had come to the fore during the historic 1910 dispute at the Chicago firm Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. The opposition called the strike against the UGW leadership's advice, and reached a path-breaking agreement with management that established an arbitration system to settle disputes.
Members flocked to the new union. Around 50,000 strong at its founding, by 1920 the ACWA counted about 170,000 members. Initially composed mostly of immigrants of Jewish European descent with Socialist leanings, the ACWA quickly welcomed members of a great number of nationalities and diverse backgrounds. Like in other garment unions, most workers and many members were women, but the leadership was predominantly male, a situation that did not change for many decades. Early on the union adopted a centralized administrative structure combined with industrial unionism, with the joint boards' by-laws having precedence over those of locals.
Espousing a philosophy perhaps brought over by its early immigrant socialist members, the Amalgamated went beyond bread and butter issues and adopted a distinctive form of social unionism that was largely absent in the American labor movement. Starting in the 1920s, it provided educational opportunities and recreational facilities for its members, as well as services such as an insurance plan, banks offering personal loans at low interest rates, low-cost housing cooperatives, medical clinics, and even union-owned restaurants.
Sidney Hillman was the first president of the new union and the most important officer in its history. He applied his experience as bargaining representative in Chicago to the whole industry. Under his leadership the union made significant strides in securing better wages and working conditions for its members, and at the same time it consolidated gains and provided stability to the industry through the widespread adoption of the arbitration system tested at Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. Hillman paid close attention to industry issues, such as production, pricing, and marketing. In order to help management meet the competition of non-union firms, the union conducted studies of efficiency, work methods, and factory costs. Letters to the official publication of the union, Advance, document the controversy that ensued within the union over what was perceived to be collaboration with management.
Hillman also understood the importance of labor's involvement in national affairs and political action. In the 1920s the ACWA sent delegates to the Conference for Progressive Political Action and to the Farmer-labor party conventions. Although many members and officers were Socialists, the union stopped short of officially endorsing the party. Communist attempts at gaining influence within the union were firmly curbed. Hillman's participation in national affairs and politics became prominent during the New Deal, when he became a close advisor to Franklin D. Roosevelt on labor and economic issues. He also served on the board of the National Recovery Administration. Later, during World War II, he helped establish the Labor's Non Partisan League. He was also named associate director of the Office of Production Management, which assisted in mobilizing the nation's resources for the war effort. Hillman's prestige perhaps reflected the healthy condition of his union, which by the end of the conflict was strong and stable.
During the post World War II period the union faced a number of significant challenges. Membership continued to grow (peaking at 395,000 in 1968), but the union's political influence and visibility in national affairs declined. In their never ending pursuit of lower production costs, many firms relocated to the South, forcing the union to engage in large organizing efforts. Simultaneously, signs began to appear of changes that would lead to the almost complete demise of the domestic apparel industry and, ultimately, to the erosion of union membership. Foreign imports of cheap clothing goods steadily grew in the 1950s and 1960s, and mushroomed in the following two decades, plunging employment in the apparel sector into a steady decline. Union efforts to stem the tide included Buy American campaigns and extensive lobbying in Congress, but they were to no avail. In 1976, the ACWA merged with the Textile Workers of America to become the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Despite successful and much publicized nationwide actions such as the Farah boycott and the J.P. Stevens corporate campaign, the woes threatening the union's existence continued unabated. The fate of the domestic industry was sealed in the late 1970s and the 1980s by the flight of firms chasing tax breaks and cheap labor abroad. By 1995, when ACTWU voted to merge with the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, their combined membership was 350,000. The new Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE!) seemed poised to infuse new life in a troubled union.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related collections: 5619: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America 5619/013: ACTWU's Research Department Correspondence Chronological Files 5619/016: ACTWU's Research Department Records 5619/021: ACTWU's Research Department's Industrial Union Department Company Records All other 5619 collections 6000/003: UNITE's Research Department Historic Files 6000/014: UNITE's Research Department Correspondence Chronological Files and 6000/020: UNITE's Research Department Records
Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; A.H. Robins Company --Archives; Adolfo Enterprises, Inc. --Archives; Airguard Industries --Archives; Airtex Industries, Inc. --Archives; Alba-Waldensian, Inc. --Archives; Alkahn Labels, Inc. --Archives; Allen-Morrison, Inc. --Archives; Allied Stores Corporation --Archives; Alpine Group, Inc. --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union. Research Department --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Research Department --Archives; Americal Corporation (Henderson, N.C.) --Archives; American Can Company --Archives; American Cyanamid Company --Archives; American Safety Equipment Corporation --Archives; Amstar Corporation --Archives; Andrex Industries Corporation --Archives; April-Marcus, Inc. --Archives; Arkwright, Inc. --Archives; Armtec --Archives; Athol Manufacturing Corporation (Butner, N.C.) --Archives; Atwater, Inc. (Plymouth, PA) --Archives; Austin Reed, Ltd. --Archives; Automatic Switch Company (Elk Grove Village, Illinois) --Archives; Balflour Shirtmakers, Inc. --Archives; Barclay Knitwear Company --Archives; Beatrice Foods Company --Archives; Benham Corporation --Archives; Bensol Trousers, Inc. --Archives; Bloomsburg Mills, Inc. --Archives; Bond Industries, Inc. --Archives; Boot Mills (Lowell, Mass.) --Archives; Bro-Tex Company, Inc. --Archives; Buffalo Batt and Felt Corporation (Depew, N.Y.) --Archives; Burron Medical, Inc. (Bethlehem, PA) --Archives; Caledonian Dye Works, Inc. (Philadelphia, PA) --Archives; Camac Corportation --Archives; Camel Manufacturing Company --Archives; Cardinal Glove Company, Ltd. --Archives; Castle Neckwear, Inc. --Archives; Charbert, Inc. --Archives; Chelsea Industries, Inc. --Archives; China Grove Cotton Mills --Archives; Chipp, Inc. --Archives; Cinderella Knitting Mills --Archives; Colgate-Palmolive Company --Archives; Colligate Cap and Gown Company --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union --Archives; Robert Bruce Industries, Inc. (Philadelphia, PA) --Archives; B.F. Goodrich Company --Archives; Columbian Rope Company --Archives; Cooley, Inc. --Archives; Cooper Sportswear Manufacturing Company --Archives; Countess Mara, Inc. --Archives; Creighton Shirtmakers, Inc. --Archives; Cricketeer --Archives; Crown America, Inc. --Archives; Curbell, Inc. --Archives; Danco --Archives; Dart & Kraft --Archives; Dartmoth Woolen Company --Archives; Darwood Manufacturing Company --Archives; DEB Shops --Archives; Design Components, Inc. --Archives; Dexter Knitting Mills, Inc. --Archives; Dorr Woolen Mill --Archives; Dothan Manufacturing Company --Archives; Dunlop Tire and Rubber Company --Archives; Dyecraftsmen, Inc --Archives; Emhart Corporation --Archives; Europe Craft Imports, Inc --Archives; Faberge, Inc. --Archives; Facetglas, Inc. --Archives; Fiber-Taxis, Inc. --Archives; Firestone Tire and Rubber Company --Archives; Fortune Plastics, Inc. --Archives; Fox-Knapp, Inc. --Archives; Franklin Mushroom Farms (Williamantic, Conn.) --Archives; General Bag Corporation (Cleveland, (Ohio)) --Archives; General Electric Company --Archives; General Mills, Inc. --Archives; Georgia Converters, Inc. --Archives; Glamour Blouse --Archives; Glen Raven Mills, Inc. --Archives; Gloray Knitting Mills --Archives; Gordon and Ferguson Company, Inc. --Archives; Gordon of Philadelphia --Archives; Greenbrier Industries, Inc. --Archives; Hale Manufacturing Company --Archives; Harding Carpets Ltd --Archives; Hartwell Company --Archives; Harvey Clothes, Inc. --Archives; Head Sports Wear --Archives; Her Majesty's Industries --Archives; Homestead Woolen Mills --Archives; Horizon Sportswear, Inc. --Archives; Hughes and Hatcher, Inc. --Archives; Hutchinson Bag Company (Hutchinson, Kansas) --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union --Archives; J.L. de Ball Girmes of America, Inc. --Archives; S. Goldberg and Company, Inc. --Archives; Inman Mills --Archives; IPC Limited Partnership --Archives; Irvin Industries, Inc. --Archives; J.E. Morgan Knitting Mills --Archives; Jamesway (Firm: U.S.) --Archives; Joanna Western Mills Company --Archives; Kennametal, Inc. (Orwell, Ohio) --Archives; Kenyon Industries, Inc. --Archives; Kindercare --Archives; King Form Cap Company --Archives; King Sales --Archives; Kleinert's, Inc --Archives; Kolortex Corporation --Archives; Kraemer Textiles, Inc. --Archives; Lakeland Industries, Inc. --Archives; Lambeth Rope Company --Archives; Lehigh Valley Throwing Mills, Inc. --Archives; Lesnow Manufacturing Company, Inc. --Archives; Lincoln Manufacturing, Inc. --Archives; Lord Jeff Knitting Company, Inc. --Archives; MacField, Inc. --Archives; MacGreagor Sporting Goods, Inc. --Archives; Magid Glove and Safety Manufacturing Co. --Archives; Major Coat Co. --Archives; Malina Company, Inc. --Archives; Maryland Ribbon Company --Archives; McAndrews and Forbes, Inc. --Archives; Megas Manufacturing, Inc. --Archives; Metal Cladding, Inc. --Archives; Miller Brothers Industries, Inc. --Archives; Modern Filters, Inc. --Archives; Mousefeathers, Inc. --Archives; NalPac Company --Archives; Namaco Industries, Inc. --Archives; National Gypsum Company --Archives; New London Textile, Inc. --Archives; North Star Glove Company, Inc. --Archives; OSR Corporation --Archives; Owenby Manufacturing Company, Inc --Archives; Pannill Knitting Company, Inc. --Archives; Pennsylvania Woven Carpet Mills, Inc. --Archives; Plausa, Inc. (Jamestown, S.C.) --Archives; Polycast Technology Corp. (Stamford, Conn.) --Archives; Prairie Manufacturing Co. (East Prairie, Mo.) --Archives; Prouvost S.A. --Archives; Purofied Down Products Corp. --Archives; Quality Mills, Inc. --Archives; Raliegh Manufacturers, Inc. --Archives; Ramm Styles, Inc. --Archives; Tony Lama Company, Inc. --Archives; Henry Segal Company --Archives; N. Summergrade and Son --Archives; Ratner Corporation --Archives; Raxon Fabrics Corporation (Allentown, Pa.) --Archives; Reidbord Brothers Company (Buckhannon, W.Va.) --Archives; Ricoh Corporation --Archives; Rob-Roy Company --Archives; Rockelman Appliance Service Company, Inc. --Archives; Rockland Industries, Inc. --Archives; Rooster, Inc. --Archives; RosPatch Corporation --Archives; Royal Manufacturing Co. --Archives; Sackville Mills Shelby --Archives; Scott Company, Inc. --Archives; Seamco, Inc. --Archives; Selma Apparel Corporation --Archives; Servisco --Archives; Shelburne Shirt Company, Inc. --Archives; Sheller-Globe Corporation --Archives; Sigallo Ltd. --Archives; Somerset Knitting Mills, Inc. --Archives; Sponge, Inc. --Archives; Stanburg, Inc. --Archives; Stanley Woolen Company, Inc. --Archives; Stedman Corporation --Archives; Stern and Stern Textiles, Inc. --Archives; Steven's Sportswear Company, Inc --Archives; Stillwater, Inc. --Archives; Stone Manufacturing Company --Archives; Stowe-Woodward Company --Archives; Straus Knitting Mills, Inc. --Archives; Superior Trim, Inc. --Archives; Textile Prints Corporation --Archives; Tobias Katzin Company --Archives; Toll-Gate Garment Company, Inc. --Archives; Tuscarora Yarns, Inc. --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives; United Piece Dye Works --Archives; Velvet Textile Company, Inc. --Archives; Versaille Formalwear, Inc. --Archives; Victor-Balata Belting Company --Archives; Viola Sportswear, Inc. --Archives; Warner Woven Labels, Inc. --Archives; Washington Manufacturing Company --Archives; Weatherbee Coats, Inc. --Archives; Webster Brick Company, Inc. --Archives; Wellinton Industries, Inc. --Archives; Werthan Industries, Inc. --Archives; Wingspread Corporation --Archives; Winsome Togs, Inc. --Archives; Woodland Manufacturing Corporation --Archives; Zayre Corporation --Archives
6766482
- 125943 Canada, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- A & M Discount Stores, Inc., 1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- A-Best Products Co., Inc., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- A-Company, Inc., 1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- A-Pak, Inc., 1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- ABD, Inc., 1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- ABI Biotechnology, Inc., 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- ALC, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Al-Jon Sportswear, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- AM International, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- ASC Colamco, Inc., 1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- ASC, Inc., 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- ATZ Plastic Molders, Inc., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Accurate Delivery Service, Inc., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Ace Textile America, Inc., 1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Adams Foam Rubber Co, Inc., 1990 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Adel Rootstein U.S.A., Inc., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Adirondack Garment Manufacturing Corp., 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Adolfo Enterprises Inc., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Advance Packaging Corp., 1989 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Advanced Laundry and Research, Inc., 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Advanced Laundry, Inc., 1990 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Adver-Togs, Inc., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- ADVO Systems, Inc., 1982-1989 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Aetna Apparel Group, Inc., 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Ag-Com L.P. Programs, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Airguard Industries, 1978-1989 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Airtex Industries, Inc., 1979-1989 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Alamar Industries (Formerly: Marshallan Manufacturing Co.), 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Alba-Waldensian, Inc., 1970-1988 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Albany International, Inc. Paducah KY, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Albex Apparel, Inc., 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Alco Capital Corp., 1990 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Alden Autoparts Warehouse, Inc., 1989 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Alden Corrugated Container Corp., 1990 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Alex Brown, Inc., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Alice Mills, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Alkahn Labels, Inc., 1970-1990 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Allen-Morrison, Inc., 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Allentown Hilton Hotel, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Allied Fibers, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Allied Stores Corp., 1968-1990 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Allied Stores Corp. (Garfinkle's), 1975-1987 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Allison Boats. Inc., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Almark Mills, Inc., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Almax Sportswear Corp., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Alphamed, Inc., 1982-1988 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Alpine Group, Inc., 1984-1990 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Ambro, Inc., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- America Enterprises, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Americal Corp. Henderson NC, 1971-1989 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- American Bag Corp. (See also Outdoor Venture Corp), 1982-1987 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- American Buildings Co., 1990 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- American Can Co., 1966-1986 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- American Cyanamid Corp., 1980-1990 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- American International Medical Equipment Sales, Inc., 1990 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- American Fast Print Spartanburg, NC, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- American Finish and Chemical Co., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- American of St. Louis, Inc., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- American Safety Equipment, Corp., 1967-1987 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- American Thread Co. (See also: Tootal Ltd.), 1972-1988 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- American Thread Co. Rosman, NC, 1978-1983 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- American Velvet Co., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Ameritex Manufacturing Industries, Inc., 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Amfesco Industries, Inc., 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Amfesco Industries, Inc. (B.B.C. International), 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Amital Spinning Corp., 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Amory Garment Corp., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Amos Shirt Co., 1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Amstar Corp. (Division of American Sugar) Versailles, CT, 1978-1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Amy Lyn Draperies, Inc., 1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Anchor Savings Bank, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Anchor Sportswear, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Andalusia Distributing, Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Anderson Mills, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Anderson Sportswear Corp., 1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Andrex Industries Corp., 1970-1990 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Angus Mills, Inc. Vass, NC, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Anna's Linen Co., 1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Annin & Co., 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- April-Marcus, Inc., 1976-1988 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Arkansas Apparel Finishings, Inc., 1990 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Arkwright, Inc., 1958-1981 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Arlee Marketing, Inc., 1986-1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Arlen Industries, Inc., 1990 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Arlington Sample Book Co., Inc., 1989 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Arm and Hammer (Parent: Church and Dwight), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Armtec, 1987-1993 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Arnold Textile, Inc., 1984 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Ann-E Fashions, Inc., 1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Art Cap Co., 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Artel Home Furnishings, Inc., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Artex Knitting Mills, 1983-1990 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Artistic Creations, Inc. (Monticello, Fl, 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Artistic Identifications Systems, Inc., 1988 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Asheburo Knitting Mills, Inc., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Laura Ashley, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Ashley Worldwide, Inc., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Aspen Ribbons, Inc., 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Associated Drilling, Inc., 1988 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Associated Student Commissaries, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Astro Apparel, Inc., 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Astrocom Corp., 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Athens Manufacturing Corp., 1986 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Athol Manufacturing Corp. Butner, NC, 1980-1990 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Atlanta Taxi Divers Local 2525, 1987-1991 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Atlantic Pattern Service, Inc., 1989 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Atlantis Group, Inc., 1989 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Atlas Corp., 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Atlas U.S. Cloth Sponging Corp., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Atwater, Inc. Plymouth, PA, 1976-1988 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Augusta Hospital Corp., 1989 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Augusta Sportswear Inc., 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Austin Reed, Ltd. (British Men's Wear Chain), 1967-1987 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Automatic Machine Products Co., 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Automatic Switch Co. Elk Grove Village, IL, 1980-1990 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Avatrac Industries (Subsidiary Of Developmental Pathways), 1986 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Azon Corp., 1990 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- B & D Plastics Inc., 1989 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- BGF Industries, Inc., 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- B.H & P., Inc., 1984 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- B.J. Paper Products, 1986-1993 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- BST Systems Inc., 1990 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Bag Specialists, Inc., 1986-1990 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Balfour Shirtmakers, Inc., 1976-1989 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Baltimore Gas and Electric Co., 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Barclay Knitwear Co., 1967-1988 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Barclays American. Commercial Inc., 1988 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Bari Manufacturing Corp., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Barnesburo Shirt Co., Inc., 1989 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Barrington Color Offset Inc., 1989 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Bass Public Limited, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- J.B. Battle Uniform, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Baxter Travenol Laboratories, Inc., 1988 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Bay Corrugated Container, Inc., 1990 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Bay Mills Limited, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Bayle Corp., 1990 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Beacon Shoe Co, Inc., 1985-1990 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Beatrice Foods Co. (Financial and General), 1973-1984 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- Beatrice Foods Co. (Clippings), 1973-1988 (Box 2, Folder 74)
- Bedford Weaving Mills, Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 75)
- Beech Island Knitting Co. Inc., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 76)
- Beech-Tex, Inc., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 77)
- Ike Behar Apparel and Design Ltd., 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Bell Sponging Co., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 79)
- Bellmar parts Industries, Inc., 1989 (Box 2, Folder 80)
- Belmont Heritage Corp., 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 81)
- Belton Corp. Belton, SC, 1981-1988 (Box 2, Folder 82)
- Herve Benard, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 83)
- Benco Industries, Inc., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 84)
- Bender Shoe Co. (Subsidiary Of B.B. Walker Co.), 1988 (Box 2, Folder 85)
- Benham Corp., 1962-1988 (Box 2, Folder 86)
- Benhil Shirt Shops, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 87)
- Bensol Trousers, Inc., 1960-1988 (Box 2, Folder 88)
- Berdon Industries, Inc., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 89)
- Berol Corp., 1988 (Box 2, Folder 90)
- Berry Street Corp., 1990 (Box 2, Folder 91)
- Berry Hill Nursing Home, Inc., 1988 (Box 2, Folder 92)
- Bertrand Corp., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 93)
- Berwick Industries, Inc., 1979-1989 (Box 2, Folder 94)
- Betlin Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 95)
- Better Brands of Atlanta, Inc., 1989 (Box 2, Folder 96)
- Bestop, Inc., 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 97)
- Bigger Brothers, Inc., 1989 (Box 2, Folder 98)
- Biltwell Co., 1983-1989 (Box 2, Folder 99)